<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" 
      xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
      xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" 
      xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" 
      version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>My Blog</title>
<link>https://www.niharikabalachandra.com/</link>
<atom:link href="https://www.niharikabalachandra.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<description>Niharika&#39;s blog where data points weave stories, and algorithmic solutions propel us toward a clearer, more informed future. </description>
<generator>quarto-1.4.549</generator>
<lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 08:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
<item>
  <title>Welcome To My Blog</title>
  <dc:creator>Niharika Balachandra</dc:creator>
  <link>https://www.niharikabalachandra.com/posts/welcome/</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 





<p>Welcome to my blog! I’m Niharika, a passionate data scientist weaving together data, tech, and creativity. Over seven years, I’ve led teams in ML, NLP, and beyond, transforming data into actionable insights for user-centric solutions in E-commerce and Ad Tech.</p>
<p>But, let’s make this journey about us. Follow along as I navigate the ever-changing and sometimes overwhelming world of AI through applied projects. This space is meant to be shared—a place to connect and learn together.</p>
<p>Expect bi-monthly posts on every 2nd and 4th Saturday. Without further ado, join me on a journey where data tells stories, and together, we explore the algorithms actively shaping our future. Let’s connect and delve into this exciting space!</p>
<p>If this labor of love enriches your life, please consider supporting it with a <a href="https://www.buymeacoffee.com/niharikaba1" class="external" target="_blank">donation</a>. Your contributions have a real impact, enabling me to curate content that demystifies the rapidly changing world of AI, fostering innovation and creating a community. This is a passion project I pursue during my free time, and I aim to keep it free, ad-free, and alive thanks to reader patronage. If you already donate, I appreciate you more than you know.</p>



 ]]></description>
  <category>true</category>
  <guid>https://www.niharikabalachandra.com/posts/welcome/</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://www.niharikabalachandra.com/posts/welcome/thumbnail.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
